[{"id":100000,"question":"What function in AMPscript is used to retrieve the value of a variable?","options":{"A":"Lookup()","B":"Variable()","C":"GetValue()","D":"Retrieve()"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100001,"question":"Which tool is used for automating email campaigns in Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Journey Builder","B":"Content Builder","C":"Data Extension","D":"Email Studio"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100002,"question":"What is required to create a Data Extension in Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Name and data type","B":"Name, data type, and primary key","C":"Only the name","D":"Name, data type, and error code"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100003,"question":"What is the main function of Automation Studio in Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Create personalized journeys","B":"Manage mass email campaigns","C":"Automate data processes and workflows","D":"Create and manage sign-up forms"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100004,"question":"What technique in Marketing Cloud allows content personalization based on subscriber behavior?","options":{"A":"Segmentation personalization","B":"AMPscript","C":"Personalization with Journey Builder","D":"A/B Testing"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100005,"question":"What is the best practice for ensuring high email deliverability?","options":{"A":"Send emails consistently without segmentation","B":"Use a purchased email list","C":"Limit the number of emails sent per week","D":"Keep the email list clean and segmented"},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100006,"question":"What is 'Email Studio' in Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"A tool for creating SMS campaigns","B":"A tool for creating, sending, and optimizing emails","C":"A tool for creating landing pages","D":"A tool for automating paid ads"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100007,"question":"How can you track the effectiveness of an email campaign in Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Using Analytics Studio","B":"Using A/B Testing","C":"Using performance reports","D":"Using Content Builder"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100008,"question":"What is the purpose of A/B Testing in Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Create emails faster","B":"Test two types of content and choose the most effective","C":"Create automated campaigns","D":"Limit email personalization"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100009,"question":"What is the function of Journey Builder in Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Create lead capture pages","B":"Create and automate personalized marketing journeys","C":"Send mass emails","D":"Analyze email campaigns"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100010,"question":"An email marketing team is setting up a campaign to message customers who register for an event. The registration data is being gathered in another system and will be passed to Marketing Cloud daily, and updates made to the customers' registration information will be reflected in the same file.","options":{"A":"","B":"Use the Import Wizard to overwrite the records in the data extension.","C":"Use the Import Wizard to add new records into the data extension.","D":"Use the Import Activity to overwrite the records in the data extension."},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100011,"question":"A marketer would like to understand how well email communications are being distributed across their subscriber base. Which dashboard provides a breakdown of email saturation?","options":{"A":"Einstein Engagement Scoring","B":"Einstein Messaging Insights","C":"Einstein Engagement Frequency","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100012,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) is launching a new product and is unsure which features to highlight in the promotion. The marketing team has created two versions of their promotional email to test amongst NTO's most engaged customers.","options":{"A":"Path Optimizer","B":"Einstein Content Selection","C":"Engagement Split","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100013,"question":"A marketer needs to share report results with a manager. Which option in Reports could be used to deliver the report?","options":{"A":"Save the report to an SFTP folder","B":"Text a link to the report","C":"Notify the manager with a pop-up","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100014,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to improve email open rates to increase subscriber engagement and improve deliverability. What action should they take to increase open rates?","options":{"A":"Include relevant preheader text in every email.","B":"Add a clear, brief, and urgent call-to-action.","C":"Use images, not text, to improve email look and branding.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100015,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to compile a report of Email Metrics across all Jobs deployed in the last six months and correlate those metrics to single subscribers and their corresponding data from data extensions. What should be used to pull this data per the requirements?","options":{"A":"Scheduled Automation","B":"List Filter","C":"SQL Query Activity","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100016,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to create an email which displays different images based on data stored in a Sendable Data Extension. What should they use to meet this objective?","options":{"A":"Data Filters","B":"Personalization Strings","C":"Dynamic Content","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100017,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters stores Last Name in a data extension. How should the text field be defined?","options":{"A":"Varchar(100)","B":"Text(100)","C":"String(100)","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100018,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters uses Automation Studio to import their Master Subscriber list. They want to enable their regional marketers to refresh their subscribers from the Master Subscriber list prior to each send. Their regional marketers are not technical and prefer to avoid writing code. Which Automation Studio activity should be recommended?","options":{"A":"Filter Activity","B":"SQL Query","C":"Data Extract","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100019,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) is building a drip campaign in Journey Builder. NTO wants to send emails at the best time for each subscriber. Which activity should be placed before each email activity?","options":{"A":"Path Optimizer","B":"Einstein Engagement Frequency","C":"Einstein STO","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100020,"question":"A marketer is injecting new customers from a data extension into Journey Builder to send an updated welcome series. They need to test the updated content and logic of the journey before publishing the new version. What would the marketer be able to see when using Journey Builder test mode for data extension entry source journeys?","options":{"A":"a manually entered test records' flow through the journey and email previews","B":"Up to five contacts' emails sent to up to 10 test emails in a test data extension","C":"Inbox delivered email and journey path for up to 10 contacts","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100021,"question":"A marketer was given a list of subscribers with various HTML or Text email preferences. The marketer wants to keep the send simple and NOT split the audiences into two separate sends. What should be selected during the Email Send flow?","options":{"A":"Transactional sender profile","B":"Link Tracking","C":"Multi-part MIME","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100022,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants a way to quickly view the performance summary of a recent email send including the send performance, open performance, and inbox activity. Where could they quickly view an email performance summary?","options":{"A":"The Subscriber Engagement report in Email Studio","B":"The Email Performance Over Time report in Reports","C":"The Tracking Overview tab of the recent send in Email Studio","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100023,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters has three data extensions used for a nightly Abandoned Cart Email. They need to automate the segmentation of data every night by combining data from these three data extensions. How could this be accomplished?","options":{"A":"Data Filter Activity","B":"Import File Activity","C":"SQL Query Activity","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100024,"question":"A digital marketing team noticed an increase in unsubscribes and would like to implement a mechanism as an alternative to unsubscribing from all sends. The team currently uses data extensions for sending emails. Which tool should they use?","options":{"A":"Suppression lists","B":"List unsubscribe","C":"Publication lists","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100025,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters' data model consists of multiple tables, including tables with sendable data, and tables that relate to subscribers, like purchases, and store location details. The related tables do NOT contain sendable data. How should their data be stored in Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Data Filters","B":"Data Extensions","C":"Lists","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100026,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to send out their password reset emails immediately when subscribers submit the \"Forgot Password\" form. Which tool would meet their needs?","options":{"A":"Triggered Send","B":"Journey Builder Quick Send","C":"Forgot Password Trigger","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100027,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters sends a monthly email regarding updates to their blog. They have noticed only a few people are engaging with the content and want to redesign to increase engagement. What is one method to apply to the redesign?","options":{"A":"Promote the blog on social media so more viewers can anticipate the email and click-through on the content","B":"Create content hierarchy and ensure copy is easily digestible so viewers can quickly scan for topics that interest them","C":"Use image-based content and skip any text blocks to ensure viewers are enticed to click through","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100028,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters recently sent a re-engagement campaign and were very happy with the results. · Delivery Rate: 90% · Open Rate: 8% · Click Rate: 7.6% What statistic from the send stands out?","options":{"A":"Delivery Rate","B":"Click-Through Rate","C":"Click-to-Open Rate","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100029,"question":"What tool should be used to render personalization strings, AMPscript, and dynamic content in an email message before sending it to a subscriber?","options":{"A":"Preview and Test","B":"List Detective","C":"Personalization Builder","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100030,"question":"A leading B2C fuel producer and supplier has just hired an Email Marketing Manager to launch its email marketing program. What tactic should the Email Marketing Manager leverage to improve deliverability when she starts sending emails?","options":{"A":"Send email during a high-volume holiday season.","B":"Send email to the most active and engaged customers.","C":"Send email to ISPs that have been notified of the new sender.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100031,"question":"A marketer has configured a yearly membership renewal journey. This journey is intended to be used for the foreseeable future. Which Contact entry mode should be used?","options":{"A":"Re-entry only after exiting","B":"Re-entry at any time","C":"No re-entry","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100032,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters has several files used for daily email sends. These files arrive from a data warehouse and are sent to the Enhanced SFTP site. The files need to be imported into Marketing Cloud as soon as they arrive to ensure near real-time engagement. The arrival time of the files vary by several hours from day-to-day. What tool should be used to import the files?","options":{"A":"Automation Studio Scheduled Automation","B":"Contact Builder Import Automation","C":"Automation Studio File Drop Automation","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100033,"question":"A marketer needs to update, but not overwrite, a data extension nightly based on data files received on the SFTP. What is required for the data to be updated?","options":{"A":"Send Relationship","B":"Primary Key","C":"Subscriber Key","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100034,"question":"The Northern Trail Outfitters' email team is creating a reusable content block for its Deals to Run With campaign. They will cross-promote this campaign in other emails in a single-column content area. This content will have one image, with text below it. How could the email team create one content area and reuse it across other emails using Content Builder without writing any custom HTML?","options":{"A":"Create an Image content block.","B":"Create an HTML content block.","C":"Create a Free Form content block.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100035,"question":"A company has one million subscribers. The company has a Master data extension that contains information about its subscribers, such as Email Address, Physical Mailing Address, Phone Number, and Loyalty information. There are 40 fields in the data extension. The data is used for multiple daily email campaigns. How should the data be updated?","options":{"A":"A scheduled automation to import a file containing all of their subscribers.","B":"A scheduled automation to occur every 15 minutes to ensure the data is current.","C":"A scheduled automation to import a nightly file of updated or changed records.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100036,"question":"A marketer is trying to configure a new file drop automation, but the folder is displayed as \"In use\" and it cannot be selected. How could the marketer update the configuration to fit their process?","options":{"A":"Change the File Drop Set Up to Use a Filename Pattern","B":"Change the name of the file on the SFTP","C":"Change the extension of the file to .csv","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100037,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters uses a Master Subscriber data extension to manage their subscribers. They send a monthly educational newsletter as well as a weekly promotional campaign. How should subscriber preferences be managed?","options":{"A":"Create filters for each communication type and select the resulting data extensions with the emails during the send","B":"Create publication lists for each communication type and associate the emails with these publications lists during the send","C":"Create a suppression list for each communication type and associate the emails with these suppression lists during the send","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100038,"question":"Once a Measure is created, where could it be leveraged as criteria?","options":{"A":"Within a Data Extract","B":"Within a SQL Query Activity","C":"Within a Data Filter","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100039,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters manually sent an HTML email to subscribers which contains a link to the wrong landing page for a particular campaign. Which option minimizes the impact of this error?","options":{"A":"","B":"","C":"","D":""},"correctAnswer":""},{"id":100040,"question":"A marketer is unable to select a particular data extension when trying to do a test send. How should the data extension be configured?","options":{"A":"Select 'Used for sending' and select 'Used for testing'","B":"Select 'Used for sending' and select 'Used for Preview & Test'","C":"Select 'Used for Preview & Test' only","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100041,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters is using a SQL query to segment customers they want to target with a promotional email send. What should be used to store the results of the query?","options":{"A":"CSV file","B":"Data Extension","C":"Filtered List","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100042,"question":"A marketer developed an email with personalized content based on five geographic regions. · Northeast—Static image of a lighthouse · Southeast—Image carousel of beaches · Central—Has no content to display · Northwest—Static image of a waterfall · Southwest—Expiring coupon How many Dynamic Content Rules need to be created to accomplish this?","options":{"A":3,"B":5,"C":4,"D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100043,"question":"A marketing team is using two systems to send emails. The team wants to maintain unsubscribe information between both of the systems. To remain compliant, they would like to update Marketing Cloud subscription status weekly based on unsubscribes from the other system. Which solution should they use to maintain subscriber status?","options":{"A":"Create a suppression workflow for the unsubscribed accounts.","B":"Create an automation triggered on unsubscribes from the other system.","C":"Import unsubscribes with the appropriate status into All Subscribers.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100044,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters has a new VP of Customer Engagement. They would like certain emails to come directly from the new VP's email address. What is required to send from the new email address?","options":{"A":"Create a Delivery Profile with the validated email address","B":"Ensure the email address is verified for sending","C":"Ensure the email address has a valid format","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100045,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters just launched a new line of tents and sent a targeted email campaign to introduce the product to its customers. Where in Email Studio could they see the performance summary of the recent email send?","options":{"A":"","B":"Overview tab within Tracking","C":"Job Links tab within Tracking","D":"Send Performance tab"},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100046,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) creates branded templates for use among its distributed marketing teams. NTO wants the template layouts to be customizable while still using Content Builder's drag-and-drop functionality. How should NTO create their templates?","options":{"A":"Populate the template with Dynamic Content blocks","B":"Populate the template with HTML content blocks","C":"Populate the template with Free Form content blocks","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100047,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to ensure its company branding is maintained on several messages triggered by purchase or direct customer requests. What should be used to directly validate and update branding in these messages without requiring developer support?","options":{"A":"Transactional Send Journeys","B":"Automation Email Activities","C":"Behavioral Triggers","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100048,"question":"What occurs when a subscriber Universally Unsubscribes?","options":{"A":"Subscriber status is set to 'Unsubscribe' on the universal list only","B":"Subscriber status is set to 'Unsubscribed' on all lists and the universal list","C":"Subscriber is filtered into an Unsubscribe list","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100049,"question":"A marketer for Northern Trail Outfitters needs to share multiple assets in Content Builder for a campaign with another business unit in their account. How should the marketer share these assets?","options":{"A":"Create and share a new folder for the assets in Content Builder.","B":"Move the content into the Shared Content folder in Content Builder.","C":"Individually share each asset with the other business unit in Content Builde","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100050,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters' marketing team includes the nearest store to customers in the template of its emails. This data extension only needs to be updated when store information changes, such as when a new store opens or a store closes. How could this be achieved?","options":{"A":"Create a scheduled automation to import the file on a recurring basis with store information.","B":"Create a file drop automation to import the file when placed on the specified directory on the Enhanced SFTP.","C":"Create an automation to begin when information changes on a store object using a workflow rule.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100051,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to automate data feeds into Marketing Cloud, and are trying to set up data import activities that kick off automatically once a file is placed on the SFTP, on a recurring nightly basis. What type of automation could be the driver of this data import setup?","options":{"A":"Scheduled Automation","B":"API Event Automation","C":"File Drop Automation","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100052,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters is setting up a new business unit. The requirements for the new implementation have been defined: · Frequent sends of audiences greater than 500k · Daily imports of large data sets, requiring greater import speeds · Triggered send functionality · API use at a later date are planned · Multiple subscriber data sets What subscriber solution should be recommended?","options":{"A":"Data Sync","B":"Subscriber Lists","C":"Data Extensions","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100053,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to send an automated second email to subscribers who engaged with the original email. Which sending method should they use?","options":{"A":"User-initiated Send filtering on _engagement dataview","B":"Automation Studio Send with Engagement Split Activity","C":"Journey Builder with an Engagement Split Activity","D":""},"correctAnswer":""},{"id":100054,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants an upcoming email to include loyalty points available for the subscriber. Loyalty points are available in a data extension and relate to the subscriber on SubscriberKey. How could they achieve this personalization?","options":{"A":"Use a Personalization string from the HTML Editor tab","B":"Use the %%_subscriberkey%% string in the email","C":"Use AMPscript to do a Lookup()","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100055,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters imports subscriber affinity data to drive dynamic content in marketing emails. The affinity data is delivered every 30 minutes via an SFTP file. They want the most updated affinity data to be used prior to deploying emails. What automation flow should be employed to ensure the most relevant email content?","options":{"A":"Schedule > Import File > SQL Query","B":"File Drop > Import File > SQL Query","C":"Schedule > File Transfer > Import File > SQL Query","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100056,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) wants to move from a batch process to a real-time process for injecting Contacts into journeys. Which Journey Builder Entry Source should NTO use?","options":{"A":"API Event","B":"Data Extension","C":"Date Based Event","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100057,"question":"Many Northern Trail Outfitters' subscribers have purchased from their website and receive transactional messages for order confirmations, shipping notifications, and more. What method should they consider to begin sending commercial marketing messages to subscribers?","options":{"A":"Add links to subscriber profile centers to opt-in to marketing communications in transactional messages","B":"Launch an automation to collect everyone who received a transactional message yesterday and add them to a welcome series","C":"Begin adding these subscribers to all marketing data extensions and lists","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100058,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters uses data extensions for sending email messages. They need to ensure when a subscriber opts out, they opt out at a list-level. What tool should be used?","options":{"A":"Publication Lists","B":"Email Lists","C":"Data Lists","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100059,"question":"During the holiday season, Northern Trail Outfitters wants to send out receipt-based emails automatically as soon as a transaction completes, regardless of subscriber opt-in status. How could this be accomplished?","options":{"A":"Journey Builder and Marketing Send Classifications","B":"Automation Studio and Transactional Send Classifications","C":"Triggered Sends and Transactional Send Classifications","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100060,"question":"The marketing team wants to ensure each email within a journey is sent when the subscriber is most likely to engage with the campaign. What should be configured in the journey so that an email is sent at the best time?","options":{"A":"Wait By attribute before each email","B":"Send throttling window configured in each email","C":"STO activity before each email","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100061,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to display the current date in order emails. What could they use to display the date in real-time?","options":{"A":"Enhanced Dynamic Content","B":"Live Content","C":"AMPscript","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100062,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) wants to craft subject lines to drive stronger email engagement. Which tool should NTO use?","options":{"A":"Einstein Copy Insights","B":"Einstein Content Selection","C":"Einstein Email Recommendations","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100063,"question":"A marketer wants to automate a data import from the Enhanced SFTP site. The data is sent from the data warehouse and is in a compressed folder. How should the marketer sequence the activities?","options":{"A":"File Transfer Activity > Import Activity","B":"Import Activity > File Transfer Activity","C":"Filter Activity > Import Activity","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100064,"question":"The marketing team at a bank needs to receive a file of all subscribers who were sent payment reminder emails and opened them each week. The file needs to be encrypted and placed on the bank's external SFTP. How should the scheduled automation be configured to achieve this?","options":{"A":"SQL Query Activity > Data Extract Activity > File Transfer Activity","B":"Filter Activity > File Transfer Activity > Data Extract Activity","C":"Filter Activity > SQL Query Activity > File Transfer Activity","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100065,"question":"A marketing team has switched from the Classic Editor to Content Builder in Email Studio. All images, content blocks, and emails were saved in one folder. How should these saved items be found in Content Builder?","options":{"A":"Create folders and move content","B":"Add tags to each piece of content ","C":"Filter based on content type ","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100066,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to automate the exporting of engagement data for all sends into their data warehouse. Which tool would they use?","options":{"A":"Schedule reports configured within Tracking ","B":"Tracking Data Extracts within Automation Studio ","C":"SQL query export of _engagement dataview","D":""},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100067,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters is storing customer data in a data extension that contains all of their subscribers and the most important information about those subscribers. Subscribers are identified by a unique field called Customer Number. How should they avoid duplicate customer numbers being created in this data extension?","options":{"A":"Set Customer Number as a Primary Key ","B":"Change to a list-based sending model","C":"Allow duplicates and merge subscriber records ","D":""},"correctAnswer":""},{"id":100068,"question":"A marketer wants to collect new leads at events. They plan to minimize the number of invalid email addresses added to their subscriber list and validate the quality of the lead. What method would accomplish this task?","options":{"A":"Add new subscribers to an automated engagement campaign, and then send a series of welcome emails based on their engagement. ","B":"Create a double opt-in campaign requiring subscribers to confirm their email address by clicking an initial email to confirm consent.","C":"Send a welcome email to subscribers within 24 hours with a link to the website, a link to the terms and conditions page, and a customer service number. ","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100069,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) is adding Mobile Studio to its marketing tools. Currently, NTO uses Email Studio and Journey Builder to send email messages. They are using a unique alphanumeric as the Subscriber Key in Email Studio. What should the administrator do to prevent duplicates across all Marketing Cloud channels?","options":{"A":"Use a single Contact Key value.","B":"Turn on Contact Matching in Setup.","C":"Use Merge functionality for new Mobile contacts.","D":"Use Merge functionality for new Mobile contacts."},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100070,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters plans to integrate their Sales Cloud Contacts. How should their Marketing Cloud admin configure the Sync of the contact object so that only marketable contacts are synced over?","options":{"A":"Select all marketable records.","B":"Select all new records.","C":"Select all records.","D":"Select all records with an email address"},"correctAnswer":"E"},{"id":100071,"question":"Which is NOT a Data Retention delete option:","options":{"A":"All Records","B":"All Records and Data Extensions","C":"All Records and Data Extensions","D":"Data Extensions"},"correctAnswer":"E"},{"id":100072,"question":"Which Contact Builder tool is used to define, organize, and relate information about a contact within an account?","options":{"A":"Journey Builder","B":"Data Designer","C":"Data Extensions","D":"Email Studio"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100073,"question":"What should the Admin create to synchronize objects from Service Cloud Mobile, pull the information into Marketing Cloud, and share contact data with business units?","options":{"A":"Create a synchronized attribute group in Marketing Cloud and link the object to Mobile Service Cloud.","B":"Create a synchronized data extension.","C":"Create a synchronized population group in Mobile Service Cloud and link the object to Marketing Cloud.","D":"Create a synchronized attribute group."},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100074,"question":"A Marketing Cloud administrator is asked by the Legal Team to automatically process certain keywords (such as “Unsubscribe”) when received as a reply to an email send, and to remove the Out of Office replies to help the team better interact with customer responses. Which functionality should they use?","options":{"A":"Preference management center.","B":"Sql query in automation studio.","C":"Tracking extracts.","D":"Reply mail management."},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100075,"question":"Which type of data extension has a send relationship and adds contacts to all subscribers when you send to them?","options":{"A":"Sendable Data Extension","B":"Transferable Data Extension","C":"Attribute Data Extension","D":"Nonsendable Data Extension"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100076,"question":"Which statement best describe a contact and a subscriber?","options":{"A":"A contact is a person who opts to receive communications through a specified channel. A subscriber is anyone you send messages to.","B":"A contact is always a subscriber. A subscriber is always a contact.","C":"A contact is a person you are going to send messages to. A subscriber opted to receive communications or belongs to a particular channel.","D":"A contact is a person who opts in to text messages. A subscriber is a person who opts in to email messages."},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100077,"question":"After setting up an automation, a Marketing Cloud admin would like their team to be notified if the automation errors. How should this be accomplished?","options":{"A":"Use a team alias in the Automation's Notification Settings.","B":"Configure a notification group in the Notifications section of Setup.","C":"Configure a Notification Activity for the team in the Automation's Notification Settings.","D":"Use a comma delimited list in the Automation's Notification Settings."},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100078,"question":"A marketing team accidentally sends SMS campaigns intended for 4 p.m. at 4 a.m. They would like to use a Blackout Window to prevent this from happening again. Which action would a Blackout Window prevent?","options":{"A":"Sends manually initiated during the Blackout Window.","B":"Sends conducted using Mobile Connect API calls.","C":"Large sends started before the blackout window begins.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100079,"question":"Which application serves as your real-time, direct line to understanding customer data?","options":{"A":"Audience Builder","B":"Content Box","C":"Application Switcher","D":"BrandBuilder"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100080,"question":"Global Conveyors wants to create, send, and measure SMS campaigns across the globe. Which application should be used to accomplish this requirement?","options":{"A":"Automation Studio","B":"Audience Builder","C":"MobileConnect","D":"Email Studio"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100081,"question":"A marketing team is using two systems to send emails. The team wants to maintain unsubscribe information between both of the systems. In order to remain complaint, they would like to update Marketing Cloud subscription status weekly based on unsubscribes from the other system. Which solution should they use to maintain subscriber status?","options":{"A":"Create a suppression workflow for the unsubscribed accounts.","B":"Import unsubscribes into a data extension, then update status with a query.","C":"Create an automation triggered on unsubscribes from the other system.","D":"Import unsubscribes with the appropriate status into All Subscribers."},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100082,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) would like to target members who recently reviewed and opened any promotional email with the subject line NTO Spring Sale.\r\nWhich feature should be used to target these members?","options":{"A":"Group Refresh","B":"Engagement Split","C":"Email Send Report","D":"SQL Query Activity"},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100083,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters wants to segment audiences based on Sales Cloud data. Where would their Marketing Cloud admin configure Sales Cloud Objects to be synced and leveraged in Marketing cloud?","options":{"A":"Setup >Data Management > Synchronized Data Extensions","B":"Contact Builder > Data Sources","C":"Contact Builder > Data Extensions > Synchronized Data Extensions","D":"Setup > Apps > Salesforce Integration"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100084,"question":"Marketing Cloud admin is asked to determine the total number of emails sent across all of their business units in the last calendar year. Where would the admin retrieve this information?","options":{"A":"Analytics Builder > Reports > Account Send Summary","B":"Email Studio > Email > Tracking > Sends","C":"Contact Builder > All Contacts > Email","D":"Email Studio > Email > Subscribers > All Subscribers"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100085,"question":"A Marketing Cloud admin has scheduled a query on a daily basis. They notice the query sometime fails to execute. How would the admin ensure a notification is received when the query fails?","options":{"A":"Install the Marketing Cloud App on phone to receive Push Messages","B":"Add their Email Address in the automation \"Runtime Error or Skipped Run Notification Setting.","C":"Add their Email Address in the Query Activity Notification Field","D":"Configure the \"Event Notification Service\" in Setup with their Email Address"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100086,"question":"NTO wants to copy journeys across business units. What could be used to replicate journey structure so it can be easily recreated in another Account?","options":{"A":"Copy activities","B":"Journey Templates","C":"Deployment Manager","D":"Journey Extracts"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100087,"question":"An email manager was anticipating a test email to arrive in their inbox. Where in Email Studio should the Marketing Cloud admin look to determine if the test Deployed?","options":{"A":"My Reports > Administrator Reports > Email Send Report","B":"My Tracking > Test Send Emails","C":"My Tracking > A/B Testing","D":"My Reports > Administrator Reports > Email Sends By User"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100088,"question":"What is the optimal way to manage unsubscribes based on communication type granted that all subscribers are stored within a single master data extension?","options":{"A":"Create separate lists or data extensions for each communication type, and create a filter to segment subscribers into the applicable lists or data extensions","B":"Create suppression lists for each communication type, and associate the suppression list with the email in the user-initiated send definition'","C":"Create publications lists for each communication type, and associate the publication list with the email send in the user-initiated send definition","D":"Create a profile attribute or data extension field for each communication type, and use a boolean value to capture subscriber status"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100089,"question":"A marketing team would like the “From Name” of a monthly promotional email send to be mapped to a specific marketing cloud user. Which feature would allow them to accomplish this task?","options":{"A":"Sender Profile","B":"Content information","C":"Delivery Profile","D":"Can-SPAM classification"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100090,"question":"What type of email send configuration should be used when sending email order confirmations?","options":{"A":"Guided Send","B":"Triggered Email","C":"Test Send","D":"User-Initiated Email"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100091,"question":"Which method of storing data allows for a company to store greater than 500,000 records, conduct data extension audience segmentation, as well as having the option to import data quickly?","options":{"A":"Lists and Data Extensions","B":"Data Tables","C":"Data Extensions","D":"Active Audiences"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100092,"question":"A marketer is building a highly personalised email which would need a highly personalised audience. How would the marketer go about merging data from multiple data extensions into a single data extensions in order to exclude an undesired population and acquire a specified population?","options":{"A":"Filter Activity","B":"Query Activity","C":"Data Filters","D":"File Triggers"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100093,"question":"What are the necessary components for creating a dynamic content rule in order to personalize email content based on customer preferences, as decided by an email marketing team?","options":{"A":"Attribute, Value, Operator, Content","B":"Lists, Value, Operator, Images","C":"Preferences, Value, Operator, Lists","D":"Customers, Value, Operator, Content"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100094,"question":"How should a marketing team create a new data extension that is similar to an existing one?","options":{"A":"Create from a Filtered Data Extension","B":"Create from Template","C":"Create from Existing","D":"Create from New"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100095,"question":"NTO has been sending emails for a decade, but their deliverability has been declining in the past year. The new marketing manager wants to boost subscriber engagement and increase ROI on email marketing. What are three strategies NTO can use to improve email deliverability?","options":{"A":"Purchase lists from companies that guarantee users have opted in.","B":"Authenticate email sending to distinguish it from spammers.","C":"Purge old or inactive email addresses.","D":"Encourage subscribers to add the company's sending domain to their address books."},"correctAnswer":"B,C, D"},{"id":100096,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) is launching a custom, corporate-branded apparel website. They are concerned about the new initiative's campaign impacting deliverability on its consumer retail sends. NTO has purchased a second IP address to be used for the corporate site's email sending. What feature would be used to specify which IP address is used for retail vs. corporate?","options":{"A":"Sender Profile","B":"Delivery Profile","C":"Send Definition","D":"Send Classification"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100097,"question":"What are three design best practices that a marketer would use when designing an email for mobile devices? (Select three options.)","options":{"A":"Use image-based text for hero graphics.","B":"Design with the most important content at the top.","C":"Keep copy simple and direct.","D":"Stack the content in a single column."},"correctAnswer":"A,B,C,D"},{"id":100098,"question":"Where can the marketing employee find the email addresses of customers who clicked on the ‘Main Banner Top’ link in the most recent newsletter, considering that Northern Trail Outfitters uses link aliases in their emails to track clicks?","options":{"A":"Tracking Click Activity tab > Link View","B":"Tracking Job Links tab > URL ID","C":"Tracking Overview tab > Clicks","D":"Tracking Click Activity tab > Email Overlay View"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100099,"question":"Como um profissional de marketing pode garantir que apenas novos registros sejam adicionados a uma extensão de dados ao importar manualmente um arquivo? Quais são as duas maneiras de configurar a extensão de dados e o processo de importação para conseguir isso? (Escolha duas.)","options":{"A":"Select the update type Overwrite","B":"Ensure the data extension has a Primary Key.","C":"Select the update type Add Only","D":"Select the update type Add and Update"},"correctAnswer":"B,D"},{"id":100100,"question":"What does a marketer confirm during a Send Preview as part of a pre-deployment checklist in Salesforce Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Confirm that each content area specified in the dynamic content rules exists.","B":"Ensure subscriber status at the time of send is Subscribed or Bounced.","C":"Identify phrases like Click Here or Free that could be marked as spam.","D":"Ensure subscribers have not unsubscribed or are undeliverable."},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100101,"question":"Which metric in send tracking indicates that the email addresses were problematic, specifically with the description \"Address is non-existent at the domain\", when a promotional email was sent to 3,100 contacts who attended a trade show recently?","options":{"A":"Undeliverable","B":"Blocked Bounce","C":"Hard Bounce","D":"Soft Bounce"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100102,"question":"What are the top two strategies to make sure that all marketers in the organization are maximizing the benefits of Content Builder in Salesforce Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Plan for content to be used cross-channel, eliminating duplicates.","B":"Optimize the way content is stored with a naming convention.","C":"Import all content up front, rather than piece by piece.","D":"Create folders for each type of uploaded content."},"correctAnswer":"A,B"},{"id":100103,"question":"Which tool should a marketer use in list-based sending to segment subscribers with the Region Attribute set as 'EMEA'?","options":{"A":"Send Flow","B":"Filters","C":"SQL Query Activity","D":"Audience Builder"},"correctAnswer":"b"},{"id":100104,"question":"How can Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) send an email specifically to all their female subscribers by utilizing a particular feature in Salesforce Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"List Detective","B":"Smart Capture","C":"Filtered Group","D":"Publication List"},"correctAnswer":"c"},{"id":100105,"question":"After receiving an email from Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO), a subscriber decides to unsubscribe. In the NTO email, there are three links at the bottom: Manage Subscriptions, Profile Center, and One-Click Unsubscribe. The subscriber chooses to click on One-Click Unsubscribe. When the subscriber clicks on One-Click Unsubscribe, what option given is correct?","options":{"A":"Subscriber can choose which publications to unsubscribe from.","B":"Subscriber can choose to be removed from the data extension.","C":"Subscriber can choose to unsubscribe from the list used for the send.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100106,"question":"What are three advantages of using Journey Builder over Automation Studio for Northern Trail Outfitters to send emails?","options":{"A":"Goal setting to have the system listen to see if users met the goal.","B":"Updating or creating Salesforce CRM objects or records.","C":"A/B testing as part of the workflow to conduct timing and creative tests.","D":"Criteria setting to segment contacts based on behavior using SQL."},"correctAnswer":"a,b,c"},{"id":100107,"question":"What is the primary purpose of using AMPscript in customizing email messages for Northern Trail Outfitters' new email designer?","options":{"A":"Automates the template creation process","B":"Automates the flow of creating email messages","C":"Provides advanced content personalization","D":"Inserts responsive content based on the user's viewing device"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100108,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) recently hired a new team member with limited experience in email marketing to manage the company's monthly campaigns. NTO is looking to avoid errors in their email sends. Which two components of the email send process can be examined using Approvals?","options":{"A":"Send Count","B":"Hyperlinks","C":"From Name","D":"Subject Line"},"correctAnswer":"C,D"},{"id":100109,"question":"The Chief Marketing Officer at Northern Trail Outfitters wants emails to look good on both mobile and desktop devices without spending too much time on development. How should this be achieved?","options":{"A":"Mobile-aware Design","B":"Desktop-centric Design","C":"Responsive Design","D":"Static Design"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100110,"question":"How should a Marketing Cloud account be set up to automate nightly imports and allow manual file imports through the Import Wizard as requested by a customer?","options":{"A":"File Transfer","B":"Data Loader","C":"Enhanced SFTP","D":"Encrypted SFTP"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100111,"question":"In what two ways should NTO respect customers' preferences when crafting emails, after debuting a tailored Preference Center for customers to share personal information like age, gender, and outdoor interests? (Select two.)","options":{"A":"Create dynamic rules based on customers' preferences in order to send specific content.\r\nSua seleção está correta","B":"Use AMPscript to dynamically pull in content associated with customers' preferences.","C":"Send customers one email per preference choice to ensure customers receive what they want.","D":"Create emails to include all preference options so that customers don't miss any content."},"correctAnswer":""},{"id":100112,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters sent out three emails for their seasonal campaign and want to compare the open and click-through rates for each email. Which tool or feature can they use to do this?","options":{"A":"Include Measures within a Filter","B":"Email Comparison Report","C":"Email Send Report","D":"Compare Email Sends on the Tracking page"},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100113,"question":"What are the two criteria that a marketer must meet when planning to send a Commercial email in order to comply with the CAN-SPAM Act? (Select two options.)\r","options":{"A":"Include a phone number to call.","B":"Include the mailing address of the sender.","C":"Ensure an opt-out link is present.","D":"State why the subscriber is receiving the email."},"correctAnswer":""},{"id":100114,"question":"How can a marketing manager personalize content for each customer in an email campaign? Choose three features that can help achieve this goal.","options":{"A":"Dynamic content","B":"Specialized content","C":"Einstein content","D":"Personalization strings"},"correctAnswer":"A,C,D"},{"id":100115,"question":"How should the email marketing team configure the import of event registration data from another system into Marketing Cloud for a campaign targeting customers who register for an event?","options":{"A":"\r\nUse the Import Activity to overwrite the records in the data extension.","B":"Use the Import Wizard to add new records into the data extension.","C":"Use the Import Wizard to overwrite the records in the data extension.","D":"Use the Import Activity to add new records into the data extension."},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100116,"question":"How can Northern Trail Outfitters ensure that their emails render correctly on both mobile and desktop devices while remaining responsive? Choose two techniques.","options":{"A":"Include @media query CSS in the email.","B":"Include style=display:block on all images.","C":"Use a Basic, Empty, or Themed Template in Content Builder.","D":"Use inline CSS styling on all HTML elements.\r"},"correctAnswer":"A,C"},{"id":100117,"question":"How can a marketing team create an automated email campaign in Salesforce Marketing Cloud that customizes the emails based on subscriber engagement, without needing SQL knowledge or support?\r","options":{"A":"Predictive Email","B":"Scheduled Email Sends","C":"Automation Studio","D":"Journey Builder"},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100118,"question":"What are the two features that can be added to code using a system-defined snippet when creating a custom HTML Paste Email in Content Builder?","options":{"A":"Link Tooltip","B":"Stored Content Boxes","C":"Track Email Opens","D":"Physical Mailing Address"},"correctAnswer":"C,D"},{"id":100119,"question":"A retailer has been collecting email addresses from customers in-store for promotional emails, but many of these emails bounce because they are invalid. The marketing team wants to implement a strategy to improve email acquisition. What strategy should they use?","options":{"A":"Double Opt-In","B":"Website Signups","C":"List Detective","D":"Single Opt-In"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100120,"question":"How can a team align column names in a file with the fields in a data extension when importing the file?","options":{"A":"Choose the appropriate date format.","B":"Name the new import definition.","C":"Select the delimiting character.","D":"Map the attributes in the file."},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100121,"question":"What feature should 'Northern Trail Outfitters' use to have their dynamically developed emails reviewed by the marketing team before approval?","options":{"A":"Standard Workflow Approval","B":"Content Detective","C":"Preview Tab","D":"Two-Step Workflow Approval"},"correctAnswer":""},{"id":100122,"question":"What are three important things a marketer should know when using personalization strings to create individualized content for an upcoming email campaign?","options":{"A":"When using subscriber data, the attribute or field should have a default value.","B":"Personalization strings are case sensitive.","C":"Personalization strings can appear in the subject line or body of the email.","D":"Personalization strings are enclosed by double percent symbols."},"correctAnswer":"A,C,D"},{"id":100123,"question":"A new data extension named `Orders` contains order data. One row is recorded for each customer's order. Customers can place multiple orders.The Orders data extension relates to other data extensions and contains the following fields: \n- OrderNumber: a unique alphanumeric order number.\n- CustomerID: a numeric customer identification number. \n- OrderDate: the system date and time for the order. \n- Instructions: an optional alphanumeric string that contains customer delivery notes. \nWhat statement accurately reflects the configuration of the Orders data extension?","options":{"A":"CustomerID will be used as the Primary Key.","B":"OrderNumber will be used as the Primary Key.","C":"All fields in the data extension are nullable.","D":"The OrderNumber field will be a Number data type field."},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100124,"question":"What tools should be used to import a daily file from a data provider's SFTP into Marketing Cloud as soon as it arrives, knowing that the arrival time of the file can vary by several hours each day?","options":{"A":"Journey Builder Fire Event Entry Source","B":"Automation Studio Schedule Starting Source","C":"Automation Studio File Drop Starting Source","D":"Journey Builder Import Activity Entry Source"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100125,"question":"How can a customer increase the number of subscribers in their account? Choose two methods to acquire new subscribers.","options":{"A":"Preselect email opt-in check boxes at online checkout.","B":"Add a Sign Me Up form to the homepage.","C":"Use a list of email addresses purchased from online vendors.","D":"Create an SMS campaign allowing customers to sign up for email."},"correctAnswer":"B,D"},{"id":100126,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters is looking to personalize their welcome series based on subscriber interaction. Depending on whether a subscriber clicks on the second email or not, they will be directed down different paths. Which activity in Journey Builder should Northern Trail Outfitters utilize for this purpose?","options":{"A":"Engagement Split","B":"Random Split","C":"Decision Split","D":"Filter Activity"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100127,"question":"How can a marketer send the same email with the same settings in multiple automations in Salesforce Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Triggered Send","B":"Send Email","C":"Automated Send","D":"Template Send"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100128,"question":"How can a marketer fix an invalid link in an email after it has been sent to subscribers in Salesforce Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"Alterar a expiração do URL na administração de e-mail","B":"Atualize o link usando AMPscript","C":"Reenvie o e-mail com o link correto","D":"Alterar o link em Links de trabalho em Rastreamento"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100129,"question":"What is the recommended approach for Northern Trail Outfitters to ensure a positive user experience for subscribers when reading their emails?","options":{"A":"Use one file type for all images in the email.","B":"Keep total weight with images at 800KB or lower.","C":"Increase DPI and file size for image display.","D":"Rely on image-only emails to engage subscribers."},"correctAnswer":""},{"id":100130,"question":"A marketer sends an email to a sendable data extension that contains a Customer_ID field with a numeric data type that relates to the Subscriber Key on the All Subscribers List as a Send Relationship. Which two statements are correct about the email send behavior for any subscriber who currently does NOT exist on the All Subscribers List?","options":{"A":"The email address and Subscriber Key will be added to the All Subscribers List.","B":"The Primary Key and demographic data will be added to the All Subscribers List.","C":"If the Customer_ID field does not exist on the All Subscribers List, the email send will fail.","D":"The subscriber will be added to the All Subscribers List with a status of Active."},"correctAnswer":"A,D"},{"id":100131,"question":"How should automations be set up so that the IT department at Northern Trail Outfitters receives email notifications once the automation has finished?\r","options":{"A":"Navigate to the Automation's Activity tab and enter a comma delimited list of IT staff in the Run Completion field.","B":"Select the IT users from the Notification Settings panel on the Overview page in Automation Studio.","C":"Add a Send Email Activity to the end of the Automation workflow and configure it to send to a Subscriber list of IT staff.","D":"Select and configure the Automation Studio Completion report from the Reports Catalog within the Reports application."},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100132,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters aims to enhance the relevance of their newsletter emails to subscribers. To achieve this goal, they first segmented their subscribers to avoid sending generic newsletters. The next step involves personalizing the content by leveraging the collected subscriber data. In what two ways can they further enhance the email relevance? (Select two options.)","options":{"A":"Use a substitution string to populate a subscriber's name in the subject line.","B":"Use a substitution string to populate a photo of the subscriber in the header of the email.","C":"Change the color of the email background to match their subscribers' preferred color of choice.","D":"Create content tailored to subscribers' interests and use dynamic rules to populate relevant content."},"correctAnswer":""},{"id":100133,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters (NTO) is looking to increase revenue from its annual footwear sale. Last year's campaign targeted customers who showed interest in footwear through a series of emails. How can NTO enhance its targeted segmentation to surpass last year's sales performance?","options":{"A":"Full-width lifestyle imagery featuring attractive people","B":"Images of products that the customer has previously purchased","C":"Personalized imagery influenced by subscriber preferences","D":"Content focused on winter sports items for holiday shopping"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100134,"question":"Which three default Canvas Activities can be utilized in Journey Builder for Northern Trail Outfitters' cross-channel marketing efforts based on subscriber responses and purchase history? (Select three.)","options":{"A":"SQL Query Activity","B":"Send SMS","C":"Decision Split","D":"Wait By Duration"},"correctAnswer":"B,C,D"},{"id":100135,"question":"How can the Northern Trail Outfitters email team create a reusable content block for their Deals to Run With campaign in Content Builder, so that they can easily cross-promote this campaign in other emails in a single-column content area, without the need for custom HTML coding?","options":{"A":"Create a Text content block.","B":"Create an Image content block.","C":"Create an HTML content block.","D":"Create a Free Form content block."},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100136,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters is considering using either lists or data extensions. Their consultant suggested using data extensions. What are three key factors that would influence this decision in favor of a data extension-based model over lists? (Select three options.)","options":{"A":"They are storing product and store data.","B":"Journey Builder will be used.","C":"They have fewer than 15 data points.","D":"Flexible data storage is needed."},"correctAnswer":"A,B,D"},{"id":100137,"question":"How can a marketer check how each email will look for different subscribers after creating dynamic content based on their attributes for an upcoming campaign?","options":{"A":"Select the Preview tab within the Classic Content tool.","B":"Create a user-initiated email to send to the list of subscribers.","C":"Use the Test Send tool to trigger copies of the email.","D":"Using the Subscriber Preview tool, cycle through the list of subscribers."},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100138,"question":"An email marketer at Northern Trail Outfitters disagrees with their creative team's suggested subject line and prefers the one recommended by the product team. How should Path Optimizer be set up to determine which subject line is more effective? Select two options.","options":{"A":"Split the audience equally and wait at least seven days to select a winner.","B":"\r\nSplit the audience equally and automatically choose the winning path based on Open Rate.","C":"\r\nSplit the audience equally and manually choose the winning path based on Email Engagement Stats.","D":"Split the audience equally and configure a holdback population for a control."},"correctAnswer":"B,C"},{"id":100139,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters is looking to grow their email subscriber list in the upcoming quarter. What are three legitimate methods they can utilize to acquire new subscribers within the boundaries of the law? (Select three options.)","options":{"A":"Email all unsubscribed customers asking for them to opt into email again.","B":"Ask customers to text their email address to a short code to opt-in.","C":"Ask customers to opt-in at time of purchase online by creating an account.","D":"Create a Facebook lead capturing form to gain opt-ins."},"correctAnswer":"B,C,D"},{"id":100140,"question":"How can Northern Trail Outfitters create a segment in a data extension that updates the data without overwriting it, and allows subscribers who no longer meet the filter criteria to remain in the segment?","options":{"A":"Query Activity","B":"Filter Activit","C":"Synchronized Data","D":"Data Filter"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100141,"question":"How can Northern Trail Outfitters effectively determine the best-performing welcome email path out of five options in Journey Builder and ensure that new entrants are directed down the path with the highest click-through rate after seven days?","options":{"A":"Use Decision Split, select Journey Data for the path criteria, and revisit the journey 7 days after activating.","B":"Use Path Optimizer, select Click Rate as the winner evaluation, and select 7 days as the engagement monitor.","C":"Use Engagement Split, select Clicks on the Message Metrics, and add a Wait By Duration of 7 days.","D":"Use Random Split, create 5 Paths with equal distribution, add an Email and Wait By Duration of 7 days."},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100142,"question":"Northern Trail Outfitters is looking to improve email engagement. What elements can they experiment with using the A/B Testing feature in Salesforce Marketing Cloud?","options":{"A":"From Name, Preheader, and Subject Line","B":"From Name, Sender Profile, and Subject Line","C":"From Name, Preheader, and Dynamic Rules","D":"From Name, Sender Profile, and Domain"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100143,"question":"How can Northern Trail Outfitters boost engagement among current subscribers based on the CMO's objectives?","options":{"A":"Create a list of inactive subscribers and suppress them from campaigns.","B":"Create a re-engagement campaign for inactive subscribers asking to opt-in again.","C":"Remove inactive subscribers from the target population.","D":"Create a re-engagement campaign for all subscribers asking to opt-in again."},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100144,"question":"How can Northern Trail Outfitters include the current date in their order confirmation emails in real-time?","options":{"A":"Live Content","B":"Reference Content Block","C":"\r\nAMPscript","D":"Enhanced Dynamic Content"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100145,"question":"How can an error in an approved and scheduled email be prevented from sending in Northern Trail Outfitters, which has Content Builder Approvals enabled?","options":{"A":"Cancel the scheduled send","B":"Refresh the email before it is sent","C":"Withdraw approval of the email","D":"Make needed change to the email"},"correctAnswer":"A"},{"id":100146,"question":"How should NTO set up the data extension for its customers, where each customer has a unique Customer ID and Email Address is mandatory?","options":{"A":"Customer ID is Primary Key and relates to Subscriber ID","B":"Email Address is Primary Key and relates to Subscriber Key","C":"Customer ID is Primary Key and relates to Subscriber Key","D":"Email Address is Primary Key and relates to Subscriber ID"},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100147,"question":"How can NTO ensure that the dynamic content block, which changes based on a subscriber's gear preference, is displaying correctly for all possible combinations, including the default content?","options":{"A":"Create an automation with a send activity that deploys test emails to a test data extension.","B":"Cycle through each subscriber's gear preference on the Preview and Test tab and send individual test emails.","C":"Create a test data extension with all possible content variations and send a test email to that data extension.","D":"Create a test list with all possible content variations and send test emails to that list."},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100148,"question":"Which three settings can be adjusted when generating this report? (Select three.)","options":{"A":"Date range parameters","B":"Error report log location","C":"Report results delivery location","D":"Report results file format"},"correctAnswer":"A,C,D"},{"id":100149,"question":"During the redesign of the company website and email design, the customer intends to maintain the logo in the header and incorporate preheader text. What are two other recommended best practices that could be implemented in the new email design? (Select two choices)","options":{"A":"Use of emojis in preheader text","B":"Mobile optimized emails","C":"Corresponding call-to-action included in primary message","D":"A mix of old branding with new branding"},"correctAnswer":"B,C"},{"id":100150,"question":"What might be the reason for the sudden increase in bounce rates for Northern Trail Outfitters after sending out a widely targeted promotional email, compared to their usual performance?","options":{"A":"They have sent too many emails recently around the same promotion.","B":"They sent on a day with high email volume like black Friday.","C":"They used \"FREE\" in the promotional content.","D":"They sent to a large number of unengaged subscribers."},"correctAnswer":"D"},{"id":100151,"question":"How can the new Email Marketing Manager at a fuel producer and supplier improve email deliverability for their upcoming email marketing program?","options":{"A":"Send email to a minimum of 35,000 subscribers per ISP per day.","B":"Send email to ISPs that have been notified of the new sender.","C":"Send email to the most active and engaged customers.","D":"Send email during a high-volume holiday season."},"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":100152,"question":"How can Northern Trail Outfitters increase engagement with subscribers who are no longer opening or clicking on their hiking newsletter, in order to improve their lower open and click rates over the past six months?","options":{"A":"Remove them from the list","B":"Request they resubscribe","C":"Send emails more frequently","D":"Send emails less frequently"},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100153,"question":"What text should be used on the call-to-action button in an email promoting the new Northern Trail Outfitters mobile app to maximize engagement?","options":{"A":"Our new mobile app","B":"Download now","C":"Download our new mobile app here","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"},{"id":100154,"question":"How should a marketing manager address the issue of emails containing images that do not align with branding guidelines in a content slot?","options":{"A":"Under user permissions, select limited template access.","B":"Configure restrictions within a Content Area for approved block types.","C":"Configure Content Blocks to only be usable within approved templates.","D":""},"correctAnswer":"B"}]